http://www.fafcu.org/privacy

Privacy Policy
SKIP TO CONTENT
ONLINE BANKING Login New User Enter search terms and press enter to search this site
HomeJoinAccountsSavings AccountsChecking AccountsMoney Market AccountsShare CertificatesIRA Saving & Term Share AccountsTrust AccountsLOANSSignatureAutoRecreational VehicleMortgage and Home EquitySKIP-A-PAYFire Station Loans and Credit CardsCREDIT CARDSPremier Low RatePremier RewardsTraditionalShare SecuredClick to PayeSERVICESOnline BankingMOBILE BANKINGeSTATEMENTSREAL TIME ALERTSMobile Depositapple payMoneyDesktopCard LockPerson-2-Person Payments (P2P)Quick BalanceVirtual CardFingerprint AuthenticationCustom Card ImagesQuick PayRatesAuto Loan RatesSignature Loan RatesRecreational Loan RatesCredit Card RatesSecured Loan RatesShare RatesMortgage and Equity RatesFeesRate Sheet (PDF)COMPARE RATESInvest & InsureInvestment Advisory ServicesOnline/Self-Directed TradingAuto & Home InsuranceLife & Long Term Care InsuranceEDUKOFE Financial ServicesFraud & Identity Theft CenterBizKid$Money MammalsOverdraft ProtectionABOUTF&A VolunteersMission and VisionF&A HistoryFraud & Identity CenterHoliday ClosingNewslettersAnnual ReportsAccessibilityEmployment OpportunitiesCONTACT
MENU
F&A
ONLINE BANKING Login New User
Privacy Policy
FACTSWHAT DOES F&A FCU DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why? Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What? The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:• Social Security number• Account balances• Payment History• Credit card or other debts• Mortgage rates and paymentsWhen you are no longer our member we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How? All financial companies need to share member’s personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their member’s personal information; the reasons F&A Federal Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal informationDoes F&A Federal Credit Union share?Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes – such as to process your transactions, maintain your accounts(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus. YES NO
For our marketing purposes - to offer our products and services to you. NO WE DON'T SHARE
For joint marketing with other financial companies NO WE DON'T SHARE
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes - Information about your transactions and experiences. NO WE DON'T SHARE
For non-affiliates to market to you NO WE DON'T SHARE
Questions? If you have any questions please call 1-800-222-1226 ext. 5990.
Who we are
Who is providing this notice? F&A FEDERAL CREDIT UNION
What We do
How does F&A Federal Credit Union protect my personal information?? To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply withfederal law. These measures include computer safeguards, secured files and buildings along with https protocol andutilization of session cookies to validate client sessions.
How does F&A Federal Credit Union collect my personal information? We collect your personal information, for example, when you• Open an account• Apply for a loan• Make a wire transfer• Give us your income information• Give us your contact informationWe also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing? Federal law gives us the right to limit only• Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes information about your creditworthiness• Affiliates from using your information to market to you• Sharing for non affiliates to market to you
Definitions
Affiliates Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.• F&A Federal Credit Union does not share with our affiliates.
Non-Affiliates Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.• F&A Federal Credit Union does not share with non-affiliates so they can market to you.
Joint-Marketing A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.• F&A Federal Credit Union does not jointly market.
Revised November 2014
COOP ATM FIND AN ATM Input zip code to find an ATM
COOP SHARED FIND A BRANCH
Input zip code to find a Branch
Discount TicketsFormsCalculatorsShift CalendarMobile DepositLost CardAuto BuyingLACoFD BenefitsFor Them it’s Business. For Us it’s Personal. Call us today at 800-222-1226. Proud to partner with the LA County Fire Department Foundation. Find Out More. >>F&A Federal Credit UnionCorporate Office | 2625 Corporate Place | Monterey Park, CA 91754Whittier Branch | 13303 Hadley Street | Whittier, CA 90601© 2020 F&A Federal Credit Union. All rights reserved.Routing No: 322078383NMLSR ID# 421486 If you are using a screen reader or other auxiliary aid and are having problems using this website, please call 800-222-1226 for assistance Contact UsDisclosuresSecurityCredit CounselingPrivacy PolicySafe ActWeb Accessibility Insured by NCUAFacebookProtect Your Home From ForeclosureE12010A9B2645221079069DBBA898DAC
HomeJoinAccountsSavings AccountsChecking AccountsMoney Market AccountsShare CertificatesIRA Saving & Term Share AccountsTrust AccountsLOANSSignatureAutoRecreational VehicleMortgage and Home EquitySKIP-A-PAYFire Station Loans and Credit CardsCREDIT CARDSPremier Low RatePremier RewardsTraditionalShare SecuredClick to PayeSERVICESOnline BankingMOBILE BANKINGeSTATEMENTSREAL TIME ALERTSMobile Depositapple payMoneyDesktopCard LockPerson-2-Person Payments (P2P)Quick BalanceVirtual CardFingerprint AuthenticationCustom Card ImagesQuick PayRatesAuto Loan RatesSignature Loan RatesRecreational Loan RatesCredit Card RatesSecured Loan RatesShare RatesMortgage and Equity RatesFeesRate Sheet (PDF)COMPARE RATESInvest & InsureInvestment Advisory ServicesOnline/Self-Directed TradingAuto & Home InsuranceLife & Long Term Care InsuranceEDUKOFE Financial ServicesFraud & Identity Theft CenterBizKid$Money MammalsOverdraft ProtectionABOUTF&A VolunteersMission and VisionF&A HistoryFraud & Identity CenterHoliday ClosingNewslettersAnnual ReportsAccessibilityEmployment OpportunitiesCONTACT
